oh Good afternoon Hello
о Добрый день Привет
discounts I live from Russia Otherwise I
скидки Я из России живут Иначе я Стрим
go Stream You are also bloggers not just So
иду Вы тоже блогеры не просто Итак
I do music I know to develop you
музыка занимаюсь я знаю развить вас
Ukrainian such
украинская такая
cool intelligence from Russia you yourself were
прикольно разведки из России сами было
Russians of Ukraine
россиян Украины
[music] A
[музыка]
friend told me that I am a Ukrainian
Мне друг сказал что я человек украинском
Nikolaev I will bring on the road
Николаев принесу по дороге
Damn  you’re tearing up the template for me, and you’re
Блин ты мне разрываешь шаблон ты а Вы
kidding me, that’s really cool what
прикалываешься вот реально крутые чего
I got
я
dirty
выпачилась
, the war started, there
началась война
was a
была
bus station
автовокзале
and
и
you decided to
вы решился
learn Toshka
Тошки подучить
Well, people were uncomfortable
Ну людям было дискомфортно
Well, then it came, we went at a time,
Вот Ну а так потом пришло поехала за раз
we
мы на Украине
pay in Ukraine in Ukraine, then it started
платят на Украине затем началась
,
приехал
you can still come to visit
еще можно побазаться
Mayor
мэра
Nastya  rudzinka tselrema tactics
Настя рудзинка целострема тактике
templates Orcs Orcs And then Ukrainian as with a
шаблоны Орки Орки А тут украинскую как с
break in the template I think about the meaning it
разрыв шаблона Я думаю о смысле это
will be some
будут какие-то
Well, you know young here in Ukraine
Ну ты молодая знаешь у нас вот в Украине
Give me people, it’s hard for me to learn
Дайте люди вот мне сложно выучить
Ukrainian Yes, because I’m a Russian
украинскую Да потому что я там русский
damn it, people chat with them Chinese  required
блин люди китайскую в чате им требуется
And here they are tenacious in Ukraine, maybe,
А тут живучи в Украине на может
in fact, Ukrainian people are still
вообще-то украинского еще люди
Russians, maybe someone is a problem
россиян может быть кто-то что проблема
l  to people in Ukraine so we can
людям в Украине так что можем
I think
Я думаю
for God those people come she is
для Бога тех людей приходит она
Ukrainian
украинского
I don’t know the
не знаю
century your dunka Ukraine in officially
века ваша дунка Украина в официально
respect wine Yes it means David rocker
уважаешь вина Да значит Дэвид рокер
in that
в том
Ukraine reserved the
чему Украина резервало
diplomacy of the bag from Russia
дипломатичность сумки из России
she was tore up the contract about we had
она была разорвала договор про у нас был
fit 97 lesson dogger  about friendship,
укладывается 97 уроку доггер про дружбу
then sleep in it will go where the power somewhat
то спи в прайдется там где сила несколь
tore
разрывал
diplomatic suckers, we also raised the
дипломатичные у нас тоже поднималось
power of diplomatic suckers, why didn’t
питание дипломатичные сосунки чему не
we break it, we also said in order
разрывал это мы еще сказал для того
to be a mission read so
чтобы быть миссия прочевала для того
that
чтобы
it would be interesting to protect them such
можно было их интересно защищать таких
Mercury
Меркурий
from Belarus as far as
из Белоруссии насколько
it has not yet been  developed, I don’t know, it’s overgrown on the
до сих пор не развивалась не знаю вот на
hand of the legs, you don’t know that it’s given from
руку ног зарос не знаешь дается что с
Belarus,
Белоруссию
our ambassador, Klykov from Belarus,
посла нашего вид Клыкова с Беларуси
maybe the simulations, now I’m recently
Может помуляции я вот сейчас я недавно
on the right, because the embassy is the action
справа потому что посольство то акция
structure, the river is
структура река
two, about the interests of the Ukrainian citizens of the
двое про интересы громадян Украины
Finnish powers,
финских державах
for example, that there is an embassy for rent
Я например в том что там напрокат
so let's say they are engaged in
посольства так и те скажем занимается
our people
нашим людям
kind kind Tabi Slava Ukra  otherwise, the first
добрым дякую Таби Слава Украине первое
word
слово
is acceptable then such a mole of the stream comes across
такая родинка стрима до попадается люди
land-based people of the Russians themselves to the Urals and
наземетчины сам россиян Уралу и
windspilks the Ukrainian language of all who
виндспилкуется украинской мовы всех кто
Until now, Ukraine has not switched to Ukrainian for
До сих Украине не перешел на украинскую
you, as if for haircuts, we are
вам моя будто за стрижки соравно мы еще
still people who are tenacious in German vegetables, she herself
еще люди на живучи в немецком овощи сама
grew up in Russian molnum Wednesday vegetables
выросла в российском молнуму среду овощи
in the Urals, I was able to get together there,
на Урале так и смогла вот сойтись там
literally less hand says this
буквально меньше руку говорит это
in Ukraine Let's give Ukraine our gold about
в Украине Давайте Украине золото наш про